

in linkedin.com/in/monica-petrichiutto

monicapetrichiutto.github.io/portfolio

☑ monicapetrichiutto@gmail.com

←39 351 622 1565

O Udine

104/08/1996

IT and Design skills

UX/UI

Figma & Adobe XD

Illustrator

Photoshop

WordPress

Html & Css

JavaScript

Language

English

French

Trip

Since I've lived for a long period abroad I had the opportunity to expand both knowledge of the English language and problem solving skills.

Dynamic Person

I can easily fit in new teams and working experiences.

Monica Petrichiutto

Web Designer and Front End Developer

I am a communicative and dynamic person. I've gained various working experiences that included contact with clients. For over three years I lived in Ireland, this experience abroad allowed me to improve my language skills leading me to have a **fluent English**.

In the meantime I discovered my passion for the Web Design and for this reason I've embarked on a new path, at first as self-taught, that includes the development of Websites managing the **Front End development** and **Web and Mobile Design**.

Education

IFTS qualification Diploma as Full Stack Designer

From October 2021 to June 2022 Consorzio Friuli Formazione Udine, Italia 800 hours course which included practical and theoretical lessons and internship for the

professional figure of **Full Stack Designer**. Main focus on **Web Design UX/UI** and **Front End** development using Html, Css, JavaScript and React. I am therefore able to develop responsive Websites both coding and Design.

Tax assistant

From February 2021 to April 2021 CAF CISL Udine, Italia

160 hours course which included practical and theoretical lessons for the management and compilation of the tax return.

Diploma in commercial services

July 2016 ISIS Bonaldo Stringher Udine, Italia

Main subjects: Law, Economics, Communication Sciences.

Professional experiences

Full Stack Designer

From June 2022 Adalab Srl Udine, Italia

Development of Websites using WordPress editing and adjusting the template's Design with related changes in CSS.

Internship as Full Stack Designer

From April 2022 to June 2022 Adalab Srl Udine, Italia

Development of Websites using WordPress autonomously managing the insertion of contents and final Design. I attended meetings with the clients discussing any changes before the release.

Tax assistnt

Da aprile 2021 a giugno 2021 CAF CISL Udine, Italia

Relational skills

Great communication skills and marked cordiality with clients, developed above all by living abroad and put into practice by carrying out various work tasks both in contact with customers and working in a team.

Personal data authorization

I authorize the processing of my personal data pursuant to art. 13 of Legislative Decree 196/2003 "Code regarding the protection of personal data" and art. 13 GDPR 679/16 "European regulation on the protection of personal data" for the purposes of personnel research and selection.

29 August 2022

Maria Patridivita